ebookinc.net 2004-06-08

# eBooks inc - Privacy Policy

Ebooksinc.com respects your privacy. Any and all information collected at Ebooksinc.com will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, or rented in any way. 

Ebooksinc.com does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, E-mail address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Ebooksinc.com collects information about its users for the sole purpose of reviewing the site and its users so that we may develop the site further and enhance its service level. This information includes but is not limited to information about browser types, operating systems, screen resolution, screen colors, and other information which we can use to help design the site. These are basic computer statistics which can only be used to make a small demographic of the types of computers people have and the area of the world they are from. 

Ebooksinc.com will make use of personal information you provide us to give you the service or product which you have requested. Ebooksinc.com will not sell, rent, trade, share or disclose any of your personal information. The only circumstances in which Ebooksinc.com will release any personal information we may hold is if:

  * Ebooksinc.com has reason to suspect that unlawful activity has been or may be engaged in.
  * You have specifically given permission to Ebooksinc.com to do so
  * Ebooksinc.com are required to by a governmental or court order or any such thing.

Ebooksinc.com makes use of [Paypal](http://www.paypal.com/) (a highly respected third-party billing processor) to handle all credit-card payments. PayPal has extensive anti-fraud measures in place that guarantee the complete security of every transaction. If you have any worries or questions about the security of your personal data or credit card information, please contact Ebooksinc.com here or consult the Paypal [website](http://www.paypal.com/).

Ebooksinc.com may provide statistics about Ebooksinc.com's customers, sales traffic patterns and related site information to 3rd parties but these statistics will never include individual personal information. 

Ebooksinc.com reserves the right to make changes to it's privacy policy at any time. Any changes made to Ebooksinc.com's privacy policy will be posted here.

Any questions about Ebooksinc.com's privacy statement should be directed through our contact page. Feel free to contact us any time and we will answer any additional questions you may have.
